拉杰 衣服标签跑出来了
Raj, your tag is sticking out.
谢谢  这是我大概两年来
Thank you. That was the closest I've come to sex
离做爱最接近的一次了
in, like, two years.
现在我觉得有点恶心了
Now I feel a little gross.
你这话更让我觉得像做爱了
You're only making it seem more real for me.
那是我老婆好吗
Hey, that's my wife.
如果有人让她觉得做爱很恶心  那也只能是我
If anyone's gonna make her feel gross about sex, it's me.
我们能聊点除了
Can we please talk about something
我悲催的情场之外的事情吗
other than my depressing love life?
那聊聊佩妮悲催的演艺事业吧
How about Penny's depressing acting career?
现在是有些不顺遂
I mean, it's been a little tough,
但佩妮是在勇敢追梦
but Penny's following her dreams,
在我心中的小本子里  那才不悲催
and in my book, that is not depressing.
谢谢支持
Aw... Thank you.
你的小本子书名是《撒谎骗炮大全》吗
Is that book called Lies I Tell to Get Sex?
这书是真的吗
Is that a real book?
如果真有  我一定拜读啊
I would totally read that book.
等你看完能借我也读读吗
Can I borrow it when you're done?
姐就跟你们分享一下
Well, I'll have you guys know
其实我上周才推掉一部戏约
I turned down a part in a movie last week.
你为什么要推掉
Why would you do that?
因为那角色太狗屎了
Because it was crap.
是我以前演过的
It's a sequel to that awful
杀手猩猩电影的续集
killer gorilla movie I was in.
《杀人恶猿》吗
Serial Ape-ist?
你不是在电影里被砍死了吗
I thought you died in that.
的确
She does.
在电影的42分钟
42 minutes in.
当时她正裸身淋浴
while showering topless,
就是跟其他学生会女生打完枕头仗
16 minutes after brief side butt
还小露了一下侧屁的16分钟后被杀
during a pillow fight with her sorority sisters.
我有过目不忘的记忆力
I have an eidetic memory.
但他忘吃什么药我就不知道了
I don't know what his problem is.
这集里没有淋浴戏
Okay, well, there are no shower scenes in this one.
他们试图从我遗体中克隆出新的我
They just try to clone me from my corpse,
但我的基因跟杀人猩的基因混到了
but my DNA gets mixed with the ape's DNA
所以我得用猩猩的巨手巨脚到处跑
and I end up running around with giant gorilla hands and feet.
是我漏掉什么点了吗
Am I missing something,
这角色不就是完全为她而设的吗
or isn't that the part she was born to play?
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
生活大爆炸
第七季  第十七集
你真的不去演这电影吗
So are you really not gonna do this movie?
我觉得这个角色对我的演艺生涯
Well, I don't think it's the kind of part
没有丝毫帮助
that's good for my career.
可是很多知名演员刚出道时
Well, but don't a lot of famous actors
不都是从垃圾电影开始演的吗
get their start doing bad movies?
但梅丽尔·斯特里普应该没碰到过
Okay, I don't think Meryl Streep ever had to say...
"得制止这双猩猩手再去杀人"的电影吧
"must keep gorilla hands from killing again!"
如果她真演了  一定也很赞
If she did, it would be amazing.
这女人真是演什么像什么
That woman can do no wrong.
我对演艺界完全不了解
I-I don't know anything about show business,
所以如果你觉得推掉有酬工作
so if you think it's reasonable to turn down paid work
继续花光自己的积蓄是正确的
and just burn through your savings,
我绝对相信你脑子没抽风
I'm sure you know what you're doing.
我觉得我们该走了
I think we're gonna go.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我们不是在取笑别人失败的事业吗
We were making fun of failed careers.
都还没聊到真正的大笑点霍华德身上呢
We didn't get to tap the juicy vein that is Howard's.
我跟你不是在同一间大学工作吗
Hey, I work at the same university you do.
是  但就像鹰眼侠也在复仇者联盟中
Yes, and Hawkeye's in the avengers,
你有听过人喊"救命啊  鹰眼侠"吗
but no one ever says, "Help, Hawkeye!"
我能问你个问题吗
Can I ask you something?
为什么你总是要吐槽贬低我老公啊
Why do you constantly feel the need to put down my husband?
他一定是吐槽出于情  贬低更是爱吧
Oh, I'm sure he does it out of love.
我男朋友不也这么对我  好让我对
The same way my boyfriend makes me feel terrible
我做的人生决定感到难受吗
about my life choices.
我们真的要走了
I think we're gonna go.
不用不用  这不是吵架
No, no, no. This is not a fight.
我们只是本来很高兴有人给你戏约嘛
I-I was just excited that someone offered you a part
但后来有点惊讶你居然
and a little surprised that you'd rather sit at home
宁愿在家闲着  也不愿意去演
and do nothing than take it.
现在是吵架了
Now it's a fight.
他们那边说清楚了
Well, with that sorted out,
我也很乐意来回答你的问题  伯纳黛特
I'm happy to answer your question, Bernadette.
是霍华德先开始的
Howard started it.
我什么都没干好吗  我就坐着而已
I didn't do anything. I was just sitting here.
我不是指今晚
I wasn't referring to this evening.
10年前  我与他初次相见时
Ten years ago, upon first seeing me,
你老公说我长得像《星球大战》里的C-3PO
your husband claimed that I looked like C-3PO
与皮·威·赫尔曼
and Pee-wee Herman.
上世纪80年代的喜剧电视  电影角色
与谢尔顿外形有些神似
而且他还叫我C-3P威赫尔曼
And he called me C-3P-wee Herman.
10年后还是很好笑
Still funny.
那都是10年前了
That was ten years ago.
在9年11个月又3周前
Nine years, 11 months and three weeks ago,
他随后又偷偷换掉了我教课的幻灯片
he followed that up by replacing the slides for my lecture
改成了一张裸身肥女人弯腰露屁股的照片
with photographs of nude fat women bending over.
你不是吧
Really?
他那堂课在教宇宙的气体云嘛
The lecture was on cosmic gas clouds.
胖子放屁成宇宙云  超好笑
That's funny!
当时我在  真的超好笑
I was there. It was funny.
而在那之后  他开始了长达10年的
In any event, that began a decade-long progression
各种羞辱  恶整  还给我订各种奇怪杂志
of insults, pranks and unwanted magazine subscriptions.
一直到现在  我还每个月都收到
To this day, I still get a monthly copy
《老奶奶床战老奶奶》
of Granny on Granny.
除了出乎意料好玩的智力游戏页面之外
Which, other than its surprisingly fun puzzle page,
整本都龌龊不堪
is complete filth.
谢谢你陪走到停车位那
Thanks for walking me to my car.
其实我也想谢谢你
Actually, it's for both of us.
昨晚我看了电影《西区故事》
Last night, I watched West Side Story,
现在有点害怕街头帮派
and I'm a little freaked out by street gangs.
为什么拉杰找不到女友
Why can't Raj find a girl?
看来这问题找不到答案啦
The mystery continues.
虽然我不喜欢你挖苦我
I don't appreciate your sarcasm,
但还有两个街区  所以我唯有忍忍了
but we've still got two blocks to go, so I'll put up with it.
你网上交友进行得如何
Whatever happened with your online dating?
没人回复我  所以我也懒得登上去看了
No one was writing me back, so I stopped checking my profile.
在遇见谢尔顿前  我也准备要放弃
Before I met Sheldon, I was ready to give up, too.
我还曾去拜访过我的妇产科医生
Once, I even dropped in on my OB/GYN
只为寻求跟人类有肉体接触的机会
just to get some human contact.
貌似我的前列腺也好久没检查了
It has been a while since I got my prostate checked.
然后我遇见了谢尔顿  你看我们现在进展多快
Then I met Sheldon and look at where we are now.
有吗  你们交往三年才接过一次吻
What? You've kissed, like, once in three years.
那倒是  你爱干嘛干嘛吧
That's true. Do whatever you want.
你好
Hello.
我一直在想  或许你和我
Listen, I was thinking you and I could
可以试着成为更好的朋友
probably try to be better friends.
是吗
Really?
我觉得我们现在就好得有点过分了
I was thinking what we have now is a bit much.
说真的  我昨晚和伯纳黛特谈过了
Seriously, I was talking to Bernadette last night and...
她说得很有道理
she made some great points.
我们都认识彼此这么长时间了
You and I have known each other a long time,
后面的我没听进去  因为她把胸罩脱掉了
and I didn't hear the rest 'cause she took her bra off.
很好
Very well.
那你觉得我们应该如何增进友谊
How do you propose we move forward?
首先我们可以停止羞辱对方
Uh, for starters, we could stop insulting each other.
这个主意真棒
That's a great idea.
本着我们休战新协议的友好精神
And in the spirit of our new arrangement,
我会掩饰我对你想出这主意的惊讶之情
I will mask my surprise that you came up with it.
总之  这周末太空总署邀请我去休斯顿
Anyway, I got invited to do a little talk at NASA
做一个小演讲
in Houston this weekend.
他们给我提供了两张机票  但伯纳黛特去不了
They gave me two tickets. Bernadette can't go.
你想跟我一起去吗
You want to come with me?
你可以顺便去看看你妈
You can visit your mom,
我也可以带你参观太空中心
and I'll show you around the space center.
我有个问题
I have one question.
这是个恶作剧吗
Is this a prank...
会不会我们一到达休斯顿
where we land in Houston
那里会张贴着你做好的通缉令
and you've made up wanted posters
上面是我长着小胡子的照片  和一个西班牙名
that have my face with a mustache and a Spanish name
于是我会被逮捕并被遣送回南美洲
and then I get arrested and deported to South America?
不会
No.
那我就放心了  因为我肯定料不到你会这么玩
I'm glad because I would not have seen that coming.
艾米  我想请你帮忙
Amy, I could use some help.
我猜猜  是不是有位
Oh. Let me guess. There's an...
穿着皮衣的男大学生
undergrad in a leather jacket
在饮水机那里打着响指[西区故事中的混混]
snapping his fingers by the water fountain.
我认真想过你昨晚说的话
I thought about what you said last night,
于是我再次登上交友网站
and I went back on the dating Web site
我看见了这个女生的个人资料
and I was looking at this girl's profile.
她太完美了
She's amazing.
她长得不错
Oh, she's cute.
还很聪明  美国大学优等生荣誉学会会员
And smart. Phi Beta Kappa.
从她没有喉结这点可以判断出
And judging by her lack of Adam's apple,
她这辈子一直都是女人
she's been female her entire life.
我喜欢女人这一点
I like that in a woman.
很好  你需要我帮什么忙
Great, so what do you need me for?
我一晚没睡给她写了一封信
Well, I was up all night trying to write to her,
我想先听听你的意见
but I wanted to run it by you first.
好的
All right.
"艾米丽
"Emily,
你的脸颊就像被露珠吻过的花朵那么娇嫩"
your face is like a precious dew-kissed flower..."
我知道  很有震撼力吧
I know. Powerful stuff, huh?
不对啦
No.
你应该做自己  而不是像个
You're supposed to be yourself, not all...
饥渴又吓人的变态
desperate and creepy.
我就是那样的变态啊  那到底还要不要做自己
Okay, I'm getting some mixed messages here.
就写一些普通的东西  比如"我看了你的资料
Just say something normal like, "I saw your profile.
似乎咱俩有很多共同之处
Looks like we have a lot in common;
-有空一起去喝杯咖啡吧"  -对
- let's get a cup of coffee sometime."  - Yes.
"喝咖啡时  我会嫉妒咖啡杯
"Where I can be jealous of the cup
它能碰触你红宝石般的双唇"
touching your ruby lips."
或者干脆你帮我写吧
Or you just write it for me.
我才不要假扮你呢
I'm not gonna pretend to be you.
我不是要你假扮我
I don't want you to pretend to be me.
你可以当我的网络泡妞搭档
You can be like my, uh, online wingman.
好比如果我们是在酒吧遇到她  你就在一旁使劲夸我
Like if we met her at a bar and you talked me up.
那我应该跟她说什么
Well, what would I say to her?
告诉她我是个什么样的人
Just tell her what I'm really like.
如果你觉得有帮助的话
And, if you think it'll help,
可以说你曾见过我换衣服
that you saw me changing once
我的鸡鸡让你想到美洲虎肌肉发达的尾巴
and my package reminded you of the muscular tail of a jaguar.
用你自己的话去表达吧
Use your own words.
谢谢你载我去药房
Thanks again for taking me to the pharmacy.
别客气  你还好吗
Oh, it's no problem. Is everything okay?
我没事  这只是
Oh, I'm fine. It's just some, uh,
为我的旅行准备的胃药
stomach medication for my trip.
虽然可能性极小 但不排除
There's the remote yet distinct possibility
我可能会沦落到南美洲
that I may end up in South America.
还记得以前我会问你一些蠢问题吗
Remember the old days when I would've said something dumb
比如像"为什么"
like "why?"
这声音听起来不妙
Uh, that doesn't sound good.
还记得以前我会指出你上车后
Remember the old days when I used to point out
应该检查发动机警示灯是否亮着吗
that your check engine light was on?
-记得  -少女  准备重温旧梦吧
- Yes. - Well, get ready to stroll down memory lane:
佩妮  你检查发动机...
Penny, your check engine...
我知道灯是亮着的  谢尔顿
Yeah, I know it's on, Sheldon!
别别别  不要啊
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
我现在可付不起修车费
I cannot afford this right now.
或许只是小问题而已
Maybe it's just something minor.
好消息是那警示灯灭了
Ooh, good news, the light just went out.
我们是各玩各的还是组队玩
Are we playing individual or teams?
组队有意思
Teams are fun.
这样的话  那我希望和我的好朋友
Oh, in that case, I'd like to be partnered
霍华德组队
with my good friend Howard.
可霍华德从来都跟我组队
But I'm always on Howard's team.
我们才是最好的朋友
We're best friends.
那种默契好到能完成对方的句...
The kind who finish each others...
-我不觉得我们有做这..  -这种事  你看
- I really don't think we do tha... - ...do that! See?
修车行怎么说
Oh, how'd it go at the mechanic?
不太妙  能借一步说话吗
Not great. Can I talk to you for a sec?
好啊
Yeah, sure.
我能跟你们一起去休斯顿吗
Maybe I can go with you guys to Houston?
现在买机票是不是有点...
Isn't it a little late to get plane tick...
...有点晚吗  没错
...plane tickets? Yeah.
求求你别再闹...
Will you please sto...
...别再闹了  好的
...stop that? Okay.
我真不知道该如何是好
I don't know what to do.
我的车坏了  彻底报废了
My car threw a rod and it's totaled.
可我工作也没了  又买不起新车
I can't afford a new one, I have no job,
现在我连试镜都没办法去
and now I can't drive to auditions.
真遗憾
I'm so sorry.
我知道这件事你不爱听
I know it's a sensitive subject,
可你能重新考虑一下那个电影角色吗
but can you reconsider that part in the movie?
我考虑了  我打了电话  人家不要我了
I did. I called them. The part's gone.
那个角色已经被别人抢走了
They gave it to someone else.
现在那姑娘马上就要一夜成名
Now that girl's gonna get discovered and become famous
然后去访谈秀大聊特聊她是如何
and go on Letterman and talk about
从一部廉价的猴子电影中一举成名的
how she got her big break on a cheap monkey movie
这都多亏了某个傻妞当初不屑去演
all because some dumb girl thought it was beneath her.
这样你至少还在访谈秀上被提起了啊
At least they talked about you on Letterman.
别这样  你想去哪儿  我都开车载你
Come on, I can drive you wherever you need to go.
怎么可能  你和我不一样  你有工作呀
How? Unlike me, you have a job.
我唯有回去当我的服务员
I'm just gonna have to go back to being a waitress...
这将成为我一辈子的工作
...like I will be for the rest of my life.
莱纳德  你麻利一点好不好
Leonard, would you wrap it up?
我们都在等你呢
We're waiting on you.
对不起  是不是我苦难的人生
I'm sorry, is the fact that my life's falling apart
打扰到您崇高的桌游了
interfering with your board game?
是的
It is.
你错了  吾友霍华德
You were wrong, friend Howard.
她完全能理解我们的状况
She completely understood.
你现在忙吗
Hey, you busy?
不忙  什么事
No. What's up?
艾米丽回信了吗
Have you heard back from Emily?
回了
I have.
太好了  说什么
Great! And?
恐怕她觉得你俩不合适
And I'm afraid she doesn't think you're right for her.
我给了你一个这么简单的任务
I give you one simple thing to do--
联系一个素未谋面的陌生人
contact a complete stranger
让她爱上我
and make her fall in love with me--
你却连这都办砸了
and you blow it!
我把你的好都告诉她了  可是
I told her what a good guy you are, but
她觉得你不肯亲自给她写信
she thought it was a bad sign
这就不是什么好兆头
that you didn't write to her yourself.
她觉得你显得太害羞  太被动了
She thought it made you seem too shy and passive.
人家才不害羞和被动呢
I'm not too shy and passive.
你马上回信给她   把我的话告诉她
You write her back and tell her I said that.
当然  等你有空的时候
You know, when you have a second.
明晚我会试着改变她的想法
Look, I'll see if I can change her mind tomorrow night.
明天晚上有什么事
What's happening tomorrow night?
我要和她出来喝咖啡
I'm meeting her for coffee.
什么
What?!
我们后来发了几次邮件
Well, we just... we e-mailed back and forth a bit,
发现我俩还挺合拍的
and we kind of hit it off.
-我找到了梦中情人  你却要把她抢走  -才不是
- I find a girl I like, and you're stealing her?! - No.
我们只是发现两人有很多共同点
We just ended up having a lot in common.
我们都是哈佛毕业  我们都喜欢乔叟[英国作家]
We went to Harvard, we like Chaucer,
我们都疯狂喜欢缝花被子
we're both hardcore into quilting.
你的一字一句都像是冷冷的酸雨
Your words fall like acid rain
在我破碎的心上胡乱地拍
on the wounded petals of my heart.
是谢尔顿
That's Sheldon.
他说他马上就下来
He says he'll be down in a minute.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
他不确认你车里没有空气清新剂
Oh, he's not coming out until he sees proof
他就不会出来
you don't have an air freshener in your car.
这个周末你肯定度日如年了
This is gonna be a long weekend for you.
明明是你要我这么做的
You're the reason I'm doing it!
我只是让你们不要再互相攻击了
I said to stop insulting each other.
又没叫你和他一起共度浪漫周末
I didn't tell you to take him on a romantic getaway.
我怎么知道你都说了什么
How do I know what you said?
都怪你和你那对"化言语为无声"的大咪咪
Damn you and your noise-cancelling breasts.
你们好
Hello.
-你好啊  -你好
- Hi. - Hey, buddy.
要去德克萨斯了  开心吗
You excited for Texas?
当然开心了
Oh, very much so.
能和真正的宇航员去太空总署  千载难逢啊
It's not every day you get to tour NASA with a real astronaut.
那个真正的宇航员是谁呀
Who's the real astronaut?
巴斯·奥尔德林[传奇宇航员]
Buzz Aldrin.
太好了
Oh. Yay!
霍华德
Howard?
又怎么了
What now?
我要去上厕所了
I have to go to the bathroom.
你不是刚去了吗
You just went to the bathroom.
我没上  因为感觉不太安全
I didn't use it because it didn't seem safe.
尽管我曾多次发邮件  马桶还是没加装安全带
Despite all my e-mails, the toilet didn't have a seatbelt.
现在也还是没有啊
Well, it still doesn't.
我知道  前面贪杯喝苹果汁时
I realize that, but safety concerns went out the window
就把安全问题抛之脑后了
two apple juices ago.
好吧
Fine.
你为什么这么心烦
Why are you getting annoyed?
我努力当一个更好的朋友
I'm trying to be a better friend,
但你不断说些烦人的话  做些烦人的事
but you constantly say and do irritating things.
-什么时候  -什么时候
- Like when? - When?!
之前在车里时
How about in the car?
我是宇航员  你知道的
I'm an astronaut, and you know it.
你只是不愿承认  因为你嫉妒
You just don't like admitting it, because you're jealous.
说实话
Well, truth be told,
我小时候的确梦想过上太空
as a child, I did dream of going to space.
那些宇航员是我的英雄
Those astronauts were my heroes.
后来
And...
你也上太空了  我挺难接受的
when you got to go, it was hard for me.
谢谢
Thank you.
因为这让我意识到
Because it made me realize
是个人就能被太空总署送上去
they'll just send anyone up there.
-你不打算让我出去了吗  -不
- Aren't you going to let me out? - No.
但我还是需要上洗手间
But I still need to use the bathroom.
给你  发挥创意吧
Here you go. Be creative.
怎么啦  害怕小小的乱流吗
What's the matter? Scared of a little turbulence?
不害怕  乱流只是大气中
No, turbulence is just the equalization
昼夜温差的均衡
of diurnal temperature variations in the atmosphere.
我一点也不怕
I'm not scared at all.
苹果汁  别出来啊
Oh, apple juice, stay where you are.
这算什么啊
Oh, this is nothing.
我以"假宇航员"身份
I experienced way worse
乘飞船垂直降落重返地球时
when I was plummeting back to Earth,
那滋味才叫一个难受
apparently not being a real astronaut.
好吧  刚才那下挺严重的
Okay, that was a big one.
我收回刚才的话  我害怕乱流
I take it back. I'm scared of turbulence!
把呕吐袋还给我
I'm gonna need that bag back.
你确定要这么做吗
You sure you want to do this?
对  我为什么不想要回原来的工作
Yeah. Why wouldn't I want to get my old job back?
看到大家一定"很有意思"
It'll be fun to see everyone.
我最后一次跟大家说的是
I haven't talked to them since I said,
"姐辞职了  奥斯卡颁奖礼见  贱人们"
"I quit. See you at the Oscars, bitches."
快点  早搞完早收工
Come on, let's just get this over with.
"早搞完早收工"
"Let's get this over with."
我这是要开车送你去芝士工厂
Am I driving you to the Cheesecake Factory,
还是我们要做爱啊
or are we having sex?
我只是想逗你乐一下
I'm just... I'm trying to lighten the mood.
-我知道  谢谢  -抱歉
- I know. Thank you. - Sorry.
真是太丢人了
It's just so humiliating.
太丢人了
So humiliating?
我这是要开车送你去芝士工厂还...
Am I driving you to the Cheesecake Factory...?
对不起  我不说了  我不说了
I'm sorry. I'll-I'll stop. I'll stop.
拜托  别这么伤心
Come on, don't look so sad.
你永远不知道未来会发生什么事
You never know what's gonna happen.
也许今晚会非常棒
Maybe tonight will be great.
亲爱的  我知道你在努力安慰我
Sweetie, I know you're trying to make me feel better,
我喜欢你这么体贴
and I love you for that,
但这让我更难受了  而且我有点讨厌你
but it's making me feel worse, and I kind of hate you.
这不是你的车啊
This isn't your car.
我知道  我想我们开你的车去
I know. I thought we'd take yours.
我不明白
I don't understand.
虽然不是豪车  但至少你去试镜能有代步工具
It's nothing fancy, but it'll get you to auditions,
至少现在  你不用回去做服务员了
and at least for now, you don't have to go back to waitressing.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
什么也不用说
Don't say anything.
我的天
Oh, my God.
你可以说"谢谢你"
I mean, you could say, "thank you."
我的确送了辆车给你
I did just buy you a car.
我承认拉杰什
Look, I admit that it's odd
不亲自写信给你是有些奇怪
that Rajesh didn't write to you himself,
但如果你了解他
but if you get to know him,
你就会知道他只是个亲切的普通人
you'll see he's just a sweet, regular guy.
作为有趣的对比  他来了
As a counterpoint, here he is,
不速之客兼大汗淋漓
uninvited and visibly sweaty.
-你好  艾米丽  -你好
- Hello, Emily. - Hello.
艾米告诉我你担心我
Amy told me you were concerned that
可能太过被动与害羞
I might be too passive and shy.
我问你个事
Let me ask you something.
一个被动的人会闯进这里
Would a passive guy barge in here
看着你的眼睛说
to look you in the eye and say,
"嘿  露水吻过的鲜花  你好啊"
"Hey, dew-kissed flower, what's up?"
不  但没有下限的变态可能会说
No, but a weird guy with no boundaries might.
好吧  这是另外的问题
Uh, okay, that's a separate issue.
咱们先把这问题摆一边  专注于"被动"
Let's put a pin in that and just focus on the passive thing.
我走了
I'm leaving.
我们周五还去乔叟读书会吗
Are we still going to go to that Chaucer reading Friday?
我想我还是一个人去吧
You know, I think I'm just gonna go by myself.
算不上是我最棒的初次约会
Not my best first date.
也算不上是最差劲的
Yeah, but not my worst, either.
我就以前对你说过的刻薄话做过的刻薄事道歉
I'm sorry for every mean thing I ever did or said to you!
我也道歉  全是我的错
I'm sorry, too! It's all my fault!
如果没有你这个朋友
If you weren't my friend,
我的人生会若有所失
there'd be a hole in my life!
谢谢你  谢尔顿
Thank you, Sheldon.
就好像剧集《萤火虫》被砍了
Kind of like when Firefly was cancelled.
但失落感没那么严重
But not as big.
机长已经关闭了安全带指示灯
The captain has turned off the fasten seat belt sign.
各位可以在机舱内走动了
You're now free to move about the cabin.
-结束了  -是的
- It's over. - Yeah.
我们是不是应该松开对方的手了
Should we stop holding hands now?
-等会吧  -太好了
- In a minute. - Okay, good.